《越狱》第四季 第四集
Prison.Break.S04E04
《越狱》剧情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
他们称它锡拉
They refer to it as "Scylla."
是一本"公司"的黑皮书
It's like the company's black book.
那是什么  可以在十码内获取
What's that? Wireless hard drive that swallows up
任何电子信息的无线硬盘
any electronic data within ten feet of it.
能接收储存在锡拉里的信息吗
And the information embedded in Scylla?
如果靠得够近的话
If we can get close enough...
就能得到了
it's ours.
如果锡拉是一张饼
If Scylla was like a pizza,
我们只得到了一块
all we got's a slice.
锡拉不只一张卡
So Scylla isn't one card,
是六张
it's six.
他们杀了我儿子
They killed my boy.
我要找出谁是干的
I need to find out who did it.
婊子  天亮了
Rise and shine, bitch.
吃早饭了
Breakfast.
喂
Hello?
科尔・普发
Cole Pfeiffer,
我是  格里高里・怀特
Gregory White here.
我会明天早上在伽特公司见你
I'll see you at GATE first thing tomorrow.
而且  我会亲自给你
And I will personally hand you
你的花红支票
your bonus check.
莎拉・唐克雷蒂在很安全的地方
Sara Tancredi's
是不是 布鲁斯
somewhere safe, ist she, Bruce?
告诉我  莎拉在什么地方
So tell me, where is Sara?
洛杉矶
Los Angeles?
干得好
Good job.
这不仅是两个锡拉持卡人
It wasn't a meeting
会面  赛尔夫探员
between two Scylla cardholders, Agent Self.
所有
It was a meeting
六个持卡人都在那儿
between all six cardholders.
所以我们已经知道
So now we know who has the other
其他五张卡在谁手里
five cards.
嘿  你从录像中看出什么了吗？
Hey. You got anything off the video?
这是在50码外用手机录的
It's a camera phone 50 feet away.
所以  画面比较粗糙
So, it's pretty grainy.
还在打印
Still printing.
你坐过那种船吗
You ever been on one of those?
是的
Yeah.
那个时候我还是个酒鬼
I was still drinking at the time,
所以  我没什么太多的印象
so I don't remember much.
嗯
Um,
他们说我那时总出丑
told I was a lot of fun.
你呢
You?
不
No.
我以前住的地方没有多少船
Not a lot of yachts where I'm from.
我一直都向往住在那种船上
I always kind of wanted to live on one.
我一直以为面朝大海是件不错的事
I thought it'd be nice to have the ocean as my front yard.
现在大海就近在你眼前
The ocean is your front yard.
你觉得我以前做的纸鸭子怎么样
What's wrong with the SS Minnow back there?
挺好的
Nothing.
你难道真想把那个放到水上
You really want to drop that thing in the water someday
让它带着你去神秘的地方
and sail off to parts unknown?
为什么不呢
Yeah, why not?
只要你和我在一起
As long as it's you and me.
你嘴真甜
I like the sound of that.
嘿 伙计
Yo, papi.
有发现了
We got something.
总有那么一天的
One day.
发现了什么
What've we got?
我们发现了一张车牌
Uh, we got a, we got a license plate.
从手机录像里打印出来的
It's a printout from the camera phone.
数字很不清楚
The numbers are
所有的东西都不清楚
fuzzy, though. The whole damn thing's fuzzy.
不要管那车牌号了
Forget the numbers.
车牌旁边是什么
What's that next to the plate?
看起来是一张贴纸
Looks like a sticker.
-DMV?  -那是一面旗
-DMV? -That's a flag.
是外交部的车牌
It's a diplomatic plate.
伙计们 六个P
The Six Ps, guys.
以前我在福克斯河管理32个
When I supervised 32 COs
小组的时候  就是全靠这六个p来实现的
back at Fox River-- it was the Six Ps made it happen.
你能放大吗
Can you blow it up?
我得仔细看看
I need to see more detail.
我正在做了
I'm already on it.
准备  计划  预防
Prior, Planning, Prevents,
无视  贬低  表现
-Piss-Poor, Performance. -How about you
别抱怨了  说说你的想法
quit shaking your ass and say what's on your mind?
那个第二步
The second step.
破解内容
Deciphering the cards.
入侵行动  我们需要计划一下
The break-in. We need to plan.
赛尔夫探员会给我们那些资料
Agent Self will provide that information.
你和惠斯勒在一起呆过
You worked with Whistler.
他有没有提过一个地点
Didn't he say anything about a location?
会不会是在那本关于鸟的书上
Wasn't that in his bird book?
但是在帝博格手里
Which T-Bag has.
如果他活着逃出了索纳监狱
If he made it out of Sona alive.
找到突破口根本没有意义
Finding where the break-in is doesn't mean anything
因为我们没有那些卡
if we don't have the cards.
这就是那面旗
Here's your flag.
阿尔及利亚?  土耳其
Algeria? Turkey.
找到土耳其领事馆在哪里
Find out where the Turkish Consul is in town.
听着  到你出场了
You know what? Get with the program.
你去找
You're up.
他的名字是埃罗・特巴克
Uh, his name's Erol Tabak.
-领事馆在市中心 -但是
-Consulate is downtown. -Yeah, but
我们进不去领事馆
we can't get into the consulate.
我们可以从那里开始跟踪他
We can follow him from there.
迈克
Michael.
我想留下来研究一下录像
I'm gonna stay back and work on the video.
好的
Okay.
-会有那么一天的  -一定会
-One day. -one day.
科尔・普发
Cole Pfeiffer.
你好吗
How are ya?
科尔
Cole.
普发
Pfeiffer.
P-f-e-i-f-e
P-f-e-i-f-e...
科尔・普发
Damn it!
Cole Pfeiffer.
你好吗
How are ya?
不对
No.
叫我科尔吧
Call me Cole, please.
P-f-e-i-f... e...
操
Damn!
这就是我们要做到的
That's what we're doing here.
这就是我们伽特公司要做到的
That's what we're doing here at GATE.
我会鼓励你们所有人
And I would encourage all of you to...
嗯
Huh.
P-f-e-i-f-f-e-r.
...f-e-r.
P-f-e-i-f...
P-f-e-i-f-f-e-r.
外交官平时都干什么
What do diplomats usually do?
也没什么事  就是能随意停车
Not a whole lot, but they park anywhere they want.
把这个放在车前面
Put this on the dash.
我们还能再靠近点吗
Can we get any closer?
就是他
That's our guy.
是吗
Yeah?
正在拷贝
We're copying.
卡在他身上
He's got the card on him.
太好了
Hell yes.
他老婆吗
That's his wife?
算我一个
Sign me up.
没信号了
You lost it.
怎么可能
How?
我也不知道
Dude, I don't know
我只能告诉你没有信号了
what to tell you other than you lost it.
什么都没有
It's gone, man.
没信号了
We lost it.
什么
What!
怎么可能收不到
How did we lose him?
我们就在他旁边
We're right next to him.
卡不在他那儿
He's not the cardholder.
在他老婆那儿
She is.
我们最好在被发现之前赶快离开
We gotta get out here now before we get made.
快点  走  走
Come on, go! Go!
我们有些共同点  你知道吧
You know what we've got in common, right?
什么
What?
我们都活在一个
We both live in the real world
没人理解现实世界里
as opposed to these other knuckleheads.
你刚才说到
So that whole prior planning
事前准备的事
thing you were talking about,
如果你有什么计划
if you got something on your mind
别人不关心  但你可以告诉我  好吗
and no one else is interested, you just run it by me, okay?
我们先这么说好
And we'll just leave it at that.
怎么样
All right.
喂
Hello?
莎拉
Sara?
我是当・赛尔夫
Hey, it's Don Self.
听着
Listen, um,
我有些坏消息
I have some bad news.
今天早上 在布鲁斯・班尼特的公寓里
Bruce Bennett was found dead
发现他被杀了
in his apartment this morning.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
丽莎  请进
Lisa, come in.
不会耽误太久
This will be quick.
我知道你有你的安排
I know you're on a schedule.
那个地方的价值现在是1亿
The value of the kip is at ten right now.
如果涨到1亿5千万 我会马上让你知道
I'll let you know as soon as it reaches 15.
当那个时候  你要马上离开
At that point, you'll have to leave immediately.
我已经整理好行李了
I have my bags with me.
我现在就能走
I could go now.
你今晚不是还要露面吗
Don't you have that event tonight?
是的
Yes.
但我
But I...
该露面的时候 还是要露面的
It's important to keep up appearances.
这样就不会有人怀疑
Not arouse suspicion.
好吧
Fine.
我对你的领导能力很有信心 丽莎
I have no doubt in your leadership
-但是  丽莎  -很好
-abilities, Lisa, but... -Good.
我对你也很有信心
Nor do I.
所以 我现在就走了
So I won't keep you any longer.
请
Please...
注意安全
be safe.
她出来了
There she is.
好吧  做你该做的
All right, do what you gotta do.
跟着她两分钟  这样才能拷贝卡
Be next to her for two minutes so the device can copy the card.
我能搞定
I'll get it.
坐下 坐下
Take a seat. Take a seat.
看见那三个穿西装的了吗
See the three suits?
像三角一样在她周围
Forming a triangle around her?
那些是私人保镖
Those are private contractors.
"公司"只会在保护
The Company would only do that
重要人物的时候才这么做
for the inner circle.
我们不可能接近她
We're not getting anywhere near that lady.
-今天不行   -真倒霉
-Not today. -Great.
怎么了
What's wrong?
嘿  帝博格
Hey, Teddy.
遇到老熟人了
Well, if it ain't the Brothers Grim.
冷静点  林肯  记着 我们需要他
Easy, Linc. Remember, we need him.
你来洛杉矶干什么
What are you doing in Los Angeles?
我想当一个摄影师
I was thinking about maybe getting me a career in pictures.
嘿  如果有人
Hey! If anyone's
有权生气  应该是我
got a right to be pissed-- it's me.
你们把我留在巴拿马
You put me out to pasture back in Panama.
让我等死
Left me for dead.
这已经是第三次了
Which makes it the third time, I believe. So, congratulations,
-那我祝贺你 你做到了  -那本书在哪
you got yourself a turkey. Where's the bird book?
关于鸟的书
Bird book?
书在哪
Where's the book?!
帅哥  你看谁在看我们呢
Ooh, look who's looking, pretty.
看谁在看我们
Look who's looking.
我觉得
I don't think
你们俩更不应该在洛杉矶出现
the two of you are supposed to be carousing around the Angel City ...
你不知道你现在的处境有多复杂
You don't know what you've gotten yourself into,
帝博格  如果你不想知道
Teddy. But if you dot want to find out,
你就告诉我们书藏哪了
you're gonna tell us where that bird book is.
你们现在就让我走
You're gonna let me go right now
要不我们就都被抓
or all of us are going down together.
你选
Your choice.
林肯 走吧
Linc, come on.
走吧 林肯
Let's go, Linc!
唐克雷蒂. T-A-N...
Tancredi. T-A-N...
C-R-E-D-I.
35英里以内
Make it a buckshot across the grid.
仔细盘查
35-mile radius.
如果她和其他名字出现了  告诉我
If she or any of those other names come up, call me.
明白
Confirmed.
你在哪
Where are you?
洛杉矶
Los Angeles.
在找莎拉・唐克雷蒂医生
Trailing Dr. Sara Tancredi.
我没让你找她
I ask for the knights, you're chasing a pawn.
她与这事无关
She's irrelevant.
和斯科菲尔德有关
Not to Scofield.
如果有人知道他在哪  肯定是她
If anyone knows what rock he's hiding under, it's her.
格雷琴怎么办
What about Gretchen?
我要让她说实话
I'm having her softened up,
但是我觉得她活着有什么意义
but I question the merit of keeping her alive.
我觉得你不应该让
I don't think you should allow...
她肯定知道一些事情
She must know something.
只要她招
She lives
她就没价值了
until she talks.
我需要你帮我做一些其他的事
Now, I have something else I need you to do for me.
好像有一个前任雇员
It seems a former employee
正在查找锡拉
is looking into Scylla.
帝博格也在这里吗
T-Bag's in town?
是的  但是我们跟丢了
Yeah, but we lost him.
他可能在任何地方
He could be anywhere by now.
他在哪不重要  重要的是他来这儿什么
It's not where he is. It's what he's doing.
他搞糟了我们的事情
He blew this whole thing for all of us.
-莎拉在哪  -船上
-Where's Sara? -The boat.
绝对的
Of course
他的死绝对是我的错
it's my fault that he's dead.
-不是的  -你我都清楚
-It's not true. -We both know it is.
我不应该给他打电话
I shouldn't have called him.
我知道的  我不应该找他
I knew that. I should never have reached out to him.
我不应该让他参与进来
I shouldn't have involved him in any...
班尼特是自愿帮你的
Bennett chose to help you.
是"公司"的人杀了他  不是你
The Company killed him, not you.
听我说  莎拉  这不是
Listen to me, Sara. This is...
这不是你的错
This is not your fault.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
有什么能帮你的吗
Hi. Can I help you?
我是科尔・普发  真喜欢你的笑
With that smile you have, I'm Cole Pfeiffer.
普发先生  欢迎你来到洛杉矶
Mr. Pfeiffer, uh, welcome to Los Angeles.
谢谢
No, please.
叫我科尔就行了
Call me Cole.
怀特先生正在等你
Uh, Mr. White is looking forward to meeting with you,
科尔  不过他几分钟前
uh, Cole, but he's just running
刚好离开了
a few minutes late.
那么我们的谈话有多久
Precisely how few minutes are we talking about?
不会太久的
Oh, it shouldn't take long.
你可以在那边坐一会
You can have a seat right over there.
对了  我差点忘了
Oh. Oh, I almost forgot.
你有一条留言
You already have a message.
我吗
I do?
是的   星先生打过来的
Mm-hmm. Mr. Xing called.
打了两次
Twice.
我想你的人缘不错
I guess your reputation precedes you.
我也这么想
I guess so.
当・赛尔夫
Don Self.
他们什么时候发现那家伙的
When did they find the body?
今天早上
This morning.
他们说是自杀
They're saying it was a suicide,
但你和我最清楚
but you and I know better.
我想问你些很重要的事
So I need to ask you something very important, okay?
布鲁斯・班尼特知道你现在在哪吗
Did Bruce Bennet know where you are now?
我不知道
I don't know.
因为如果他知道的话
Because if he did,
公司现在就有好机会来行动
there's a damn good chance that the Company does now too.Okay?
所以你现在要加倍努力
So you need to work double time.
自己小心点  明白吗
Get some eyes in the back of your head, you understand?
我感谢你的鼓励
Look, I appreciate the motivational speech,
那你能告诉我
but how about you figure out
我们在哪才能找到那6张卡并且破译它吗
where we have to break in so we can decode those cards?
行了  我了解
I've, I've got
大家都在干活  对吧
some guys doing some digging, okay?
实际上  有两帮人给你干活
Actually, you might have two.
什么  你说什么呢
Well, what are you... what are you talking about?
他名叫帝博格
His name is Theodore Bagwell.
在巴拿马的时候和我们在一起
He was with us in Panama,
现在他就在洛杉矶
and now he's here in Los Angeles,
他有一本曾经属于惠斯勒的书
and he has a book that used to belong
马宏认为
to Whistler, and Mahone thinks...
那本书对我们有利
Mahone thinks this book has a plan for the break-in.
你开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
我也希望是玩笑
I wish I were.
这里是贾斯帕・波茨
You've reached Jasper Potts.
请留言
Leave a message.
是我  听着
Hey, it's me. Listen, I need that information
我需要我们昨天讨论过的资料
we talked about, like yesterday, you understand?,
尽快的给我回电
Call me back. Call... me... back as soon as possible.
丽莎・特巴克 土耳其领事的妻子
Lisa Tabak. Wife of the Turkish Consul.
结婚4年  没有孩子
Married four years, children-- none.
行政档案上列出
Listed as the logistician
她还是物流师
in the executive profile for SENSA,
和私人基金理财师  办公地点设在华盛顿  纽约
a privately funded think tank with offices in D.C,
芝加哥和洛杉矶
New York, Chicago and Los Angeles.
我只想知道的是
Yeah, and the only thing
她的日程表
I want to know about this chick is her schedule.
她在做什么  往哪去
What she's doing, where she's going.
我们可能没有那么多时间了
We might not have that kind of time.
今天早上她出车门的时候
This morning, when she first got out of the car,
带着手提箱
she had a suitcase.
查一下航空公司的航班记录
Well, let's check the airlines, match her name against
再查查她的名字
aparting flights.
说不定她已经走了
Maybe she's already gone.
不一定
I don't think so.
如果她今天要去哪儿
If she's going anywhere today,
她肯定会坐夜间航班
it's gonna be on the red eye.
从新闻上看  她在一些市里的慈善组织中
According to this press release, Lisa Tabak is being honored
很受尊敬
at some charity shindig downtown.
不错  那就是我们能找到她的地方
Well, that's great. That's where we'll get her.
她目的是什么
What's the benefit for?
他是雄鹰和天使组织的
She's the top donor of an organization
最大投资人
called Eagles and Angels.
雄鹰和天使
Eagles and Angels?
你听说过吗
You've heard of it?
当警官因公殉职时
When a police officer dies in the line of duty,
他被称为雄鹰
he's an Eagle.
他留下来的人就叫做天使
The ones he leaves behind are Angels.
这是个有益于执法的社团啊
That's a benefit for the Association of Law Enforcement.
如果想接近她
If you're gonna get near her,
那会招来洛杉矶市的半数警察
it's gonna be with about half the cops in L.A.
贾斯帕  你死哪儿去了
Jasper, where the hell you been?
- 思考  - 你想什么?
-Thinking.  -Thinking?
拜托  你现在最要想的是
Come on, the only thing you ould be thinking about
我要你为我找的东西
is what I asked you to get for me.
你找到那个位置了吗
Did you find the location?
是的  别再说废话了行吗
Yes, yes, and don't say anything else, okay?
我昨天听到手机响了
I heard clicks yesterday on my phone.
好的  别紧张  我马上就来
All right, settle down, all right? I'm coming to you.
没事  你是不可能进去的
It doesn't matter, you know, cause you're never gonna
那不是他们的地方
be able to get in, not where they're keeping it.
我真不该帮你的
I should have never helped you out. I...
冷静好吗  我马上就到你那
Just relax, okay? I'm coming to you right now.
这些够厉害吗
Think they're strong enough?
放一起应该可以
Together they should be.
这些就是单子上的所有东西
That's everything on the list.
我们一定要去偷吗
You sure we have to steal them?
这些都是我们需要的  商店买不到
It's the one thing we need that we can't get at a store,
兄弟  我们必须去偷
buddy, so yes, we got to steal them.
我们拿到了所有的东西就和你们在那碰头
We'll get everything else and meet you there.
好的
All right.
嘿
Look, um,
你没事吧
you gonna be okay?
是的 我只是需要时间
Yeah. I just need time.
好的
Right.
我尽快回来
I'll be back as soon as I can.
好的
Okay.
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry
我下个星期不能待在这里
I'm not going to be around next week
看你的表现科尔
to see you in action, Cole,
但是你有安迪在这里给你当帮手
but you' be in good hands with Andy here.
我要赶去旧金山的飞机
I have got to catch a flight to San Francisco,
但是我要告诉你 你能来这里
but I just wanted to say how thrilled we are
我们真是太激动了 希望其他
to have you here, and hopefully, some of the rest
人能从你这学到点销售本领
of the sales force can learn a thing or two.
在我回来后再解决支票的问题  怎么样
Uh, we'll settle up that check when I get back, all right?
记住了 别喊我弗里斯科了
Uh, remember, don't call it Frisco.
我讨厌那个叫法
They hate that up there.
没问题
True.
好  就让我领你看看你的办公室吧  科尔
Well, why don't I show you to your office, Cole?
-好的  -不好意思
-Okeydoke. -I'm sorry.
我从没有看到关于你是
I didn't see anywhere in your paperwork
残疾人的书面材料
that you were... handicapped.
不然的话 我对你办公的地方做一些
Otherwise, I would have made the necessary adjustments
必要的调整
to your work space.
安迪 我觉得自己是一个
Andy, I like to think of myself as...
"残疾全能人"
handicapable.
绝对是
Right. Yeah.
就是这里了
Well, here you are.
好的 好的
Right, right.
这就是我将要工作的
So this is where I'm gonna be doing my, uh...
我就要在这里工作的
my work, right here in this, uh...
办公室
...office.
没错
That's right.
看来我要开始卷起我的袖子了
So, I'd better be rolling  my sleeves, then.
你知道吧  科尔  我不得不告诉你
You know, Cole, I-I got to tell you.
我还是觉得很惊奇
I'm still a little amazed
我从没见过像你这样的例子
at somebody I've never even seen at a convention
简直像从天而降一样
or seminar just falls from the sky
打破了我们所有的销售记录
and shatters all of our sales records.
当你和我一样相信伽特公司
When you believe in GATE like I do,
想做销售就不那么难了
it ain't that hard to sell.
说的对
There you go.
好的
Well.
这就是你要求的转角办公室
And here's your corner office as requested.
欢迎加入团队
Welcome to the team.
好的  谢谢了
All righty, then. Thank you.
One...
22...
...B
...B.
哦
Oh.
你好  莎拉
Hello, Sara.
莎拉  你去哪
Hey, Sara, where you going?
来点什么
What can I get you?
苏打水  谢谢
Club soda, please.
多少年了
How many years?
什么
Sorry?
你参加戒酒计划
In the program. How many years
有多少个年头了
have you been sober?
三年又三个月了
About three years and three months.
很好啊
Good for you.
是啊  今天感觉不好
Yeah, it doesn't feel good today.
但是如果
But I'll take
解决了这个大问题后我会非常高兴
the high five for cracking the big question.
什么问题
Which is?
生活是场悲剧吗
Is life a tragedy,
或者还有
or is there...
希望
...hope?
你告诉我
You tell me.
双份波旁威士忌  不加水
Double bourbon, neat.
倒吧
Just pour it.
干杯  甜心
Cheers, honey.
这里
Over here.
雄鹰和天使组织里是对公司有贡献的人
Eagles and Angels, with contributions from the Company.
再过五分钟就差不多要开始了
This thing's supposed to start in five minutes.
-不好意思  对不起  -没关系
Excuse me, sorry. No problem.
你在哪个部门工作
Where do you work out of?
那里有我的一个手下
That's one of my guys up there.
不好意思  我只是
I'm sorry, I just...
没关系
Oh, sure, sure.
Of course.
我生下来就知道他了
I've known him my whole life.
他是我家的一个非常亲密的朋友
He was a very close person to my family.
总有一些好人
It's always the good ones.
你不喝吗
You ain't gonna drink that?
甜心
Honey
好好先生谢尔帕德现在就能减轻你的痛苦
the Good Shepard is here to ease your pain.
罗纳德・温斯顿・谢尔帕德  你可以喊我谢尔
Ronald Winston Shepard-- you can call me Shep.
谢尔  我现在真的不想说话
Shep, I really don't feel like talking right now.
你一直在和她说话
You've been talking to her.
让她清净会好吧
Leave her alone, okay?
不好意思
Pardon me.
继续
Go on.
当我13岁时我要去见音乐家安妮
When I was 13, I had to go see Annie, the musical,
但是我的妈妈在那年早些时候去世了
but my mom had passed away
我爸爸答应带我去
earlier that year and my dad had agreed to take me and...
我都换上新衣服了
I was all ready in my new drs,
并且我详细的记得关于这事情
and, uh, and I knew every word of this thing.
我爸从公司打电话来
And my dad called from work,
说他没时间带我去
and he said he wasn't going to make it.
那已不是第一次
That wasn't the first time.
我记得  感觉自己像在独自飘零
And I remember feeling like I was floating...
好像自己是世上唯一的一个人
like I was the only person in the whole world.
这时布鲁斯来了
And Bruce came.
他出现了  带着我
He showed up to take me and...
之后  他又带我回家  他说
And after, he took me home, and he said
如果我需要他  他都会帮我
that if I ever needed him, he'd be there for me.
一个月前  我需要他帮忙  打电话给他
And a month ago, I needed him, and I called him.
而他因此丧命
And he died for it.
等等
Just a sec.
他会让你怎么做
What would he want you to do?
我来帮你吧
Let me do you a favor.
在我们就坐用餐前
Uh, before we sit down to eat,
欢迎各位参加
I'd like to welcome everyone
第15届年度飞鹰天使慈善宴会
to the 15th Annual Eagles and Angels Benefit.
我们都知道今晚聚餐的目的
We all know why we're here tonight,
我希望先进行默哀时刻
so I'd like to begin with a moment of silence
重申我们对法律的贡献
to renew our dedication to the law
并向那些无畏追求公正
and to honor those whose lives were cut short
英明早逝的同志们致哀
by their fearless pursuit of justice.
我们会将他们铭记在心
They will truly be missed.
谢谢
Thank you.
用餐愉快
Enjoy your dinner.
我被认出来了  伙计们
I've been made, guys.
只管复制卡
Just get the card copy.
开始了
Here we go.
正在复制
We're copying
节哀
Hi, my condolences.
喂
Yes?
15点启程
The kip's at 15.
我明白
I understand.
我很抱歉  但我得先走了
I'm very sorry, but I'm going to have to leave.
我很抱歉  对
Yeah. I'm so sorry. Yes.
她想干什么?
What's she doing?
她要走了
She's leaving.
我很抱歉
I'm... so sorry.
喂
Yeah?
我被发现了  在后门等我
I've been made. Meet me out back.
走
Go.
林肯・布伦斯
Lincoln Burrows.
我不知道你说谁
I don't who you think I am.
我知道你是谁  现在把枪套解开
I know who you are. Now put the gun slowy.
3号  呼叫
Three. Copy?
走
Move.
Move it.
该把装置拿回来了
Time to get the device.
够了
That's far enough.
你为何不叫个警察来?
Why don't you just call one of the cops?
我们为公司卖命  布伦斯  我们不需要警察
We work for the Company, Burrows. We don't need cops.
准备好遗言了吗
Got any last words?
喂
Yeah?
我们有麻烦了  我刚杀了一个保镖
We got a problem. I just killed one of the guards.
我们快走吧
Let's go now!
不  我们还没拿到手
No. We don't have it yet.
你继续想办法
Do what you got to do.
我们得处理尸体
We got to get rid of the body.
让他们找到他
Let them find him.
什么?
What?
等马宏
Wait for Mahone.
格雷琴
Gretchen.
美女感觉如何
How's my girl?
看来不止你的朋友
It seems your friend Whistler
惠斯勒在找锡拉
wasn't the only one looking into Scylla.
你知道这事吗
You know anything about that?
不
No
No.
你什么也不知道  对吧
You never know anything, do you?
你跟这些事都没关系
You have nothing to do with any of this.
斯科菲尔德  布伦斯
Scofield, Burrows...
你不知道  谁...
You don't know who...
不
No.
你不能一直对我撒谎
You can't keep lying to me.
不
No!
我不知道
I don't know!
你看上去...
You look so...
相当轻松
...damn easy.
我会让你痛苦点
I can make this a lot harder.
喂
Yes.
布鲁斯・班尼特的一张信用卡
A credit card belonging to Bruce Bennett
刚在圣佩德罗的一间酒吧消费过
was just used at a bar in San Pedro.
谢谢  很贴心
Thank you. It's lovely.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我们在外面找到一具死尸
we have a DOA outside,
我想是你们的一个手下
I believe it's one of your men.
你得跟我去一趟
You need to come with me.
什么?
Excuse me?
在你确认他身份前  谁都不能离开
No one's leaving here until you make an ID.
请
Please.
玛瑟斯
Mathers.
请跟特巴克夫人呆在一起
Stay with Mrs. Tabak.
怎么回事?  我要赶飞机
Uh, what hpened? I have a plane to catch.
我明白  我们很快就解决
I understand. We'll make this fast.
玛瑟斯警官会跟你留在这
Officer Mathers, he'll wait with you.
请  跟她呆在这
Please. Stay with her.
麻烦跟我在这稍等  夫人
If you could just wait with me, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
只耽误几分钟而已
Should only take a few minutes.
真是个不错的纪念方式啊
This is a nice memorial.
我真的很佩服
I very much respect
你们所做出的牺牲
the sacrifices you men make.
那里的坏人可多着呢
There's a lot of bad people out there.
玛瑟斯长官  你...
Officer Mathers, you, um...
你脸上有东西
you have something.
你的...你的鼻子在流血
Your, your nose is bleeding.
总有一天...
One day...
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我在找这个女人
I'm looking for this woman.
来  拿着
Here, take that.
你没事吧
You okay?
妈的  没事
Hell, yes.
没什么的  旅途顺利
It's nothing. Travel safely.
特巴克夫人  我们得走了
Mrs. Tabak, we've got to leave.
夫人  快走
Ma'am, now.
告诉你  我没有见到她
I'm telling you, I haven't seen her.
你确信?
You're sure?
大家小心
Oh, look out, fellas!
是那些猪头来了  快跑!
It's the pigs! Run!
闭嘴  混蛋
Shut up, wiseass.
你确信你拿到所有的东西了?
You're sure you got the whole thing?
百分百确信
A hundred percent.
莎拉在哪?
Where's Sara?
我又不是负责看她的
It's not my turn to watch her.
我们到底要干吗  肯定有人看见我们了
What the hell are we gonna do? Someone must've seen us.
别急  应付得了
Don't worry, it's handled.
政治针对行动?
Politically motivated?
他们认为和那些亚美尼亚人有关系
They think it had something to do with the Armenians.
迪普进了洛杉矶警察局
Tip came in to LAPD.
杀手以为领事...
The assailant thought the consul
在那里
was at the event.
丽莎的贴身保镖挡了路
Lisa's bodyguard got in the way.
丽莎坐那个航班了吗
Did Lisa make her flight?
是的  将军
Yes, General.
你找到什么了
What do you got?
一个人
I had a guy.
真的  我有这么一个人
I did. I had a guy.
他...是个告密者
He, uh, was an informant.
事实上  他给公司服务了...
Actually, he used to work for the Company
十一年  直到现在...
for about 11 years until he
他决定帮助我们一起抵抗公司
turned against them and decided to help me.
他有我们要的地点
He said he had the location we needed.
但是我...
But I, uh...
今天发现他已经死在他的公寓了
found him dead in his apartment today.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
先是班尼特  现在就轮到你们了
First Bennett, now your guy, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
他们咄咄逼人啊
They're closing in on us.
毫无疑问
There's no doubt about it,
而且现在  我也是...
and now, I'm, uh...
两手空空  束手无策了
empty-handed.
我也不知道去哪里...
And now I have no idea where we need
找突破点
to break into.
我们这样继续追寻
We keep moving forward, ent Self.
却什么都没改变
Nothing changes.
-不管做了什么  -是啊
-No matter what. -Right.
好了
Okay .
不管发生什么  我...
Regardless of what happens, I, uh,
我都支持你  斯科菲尔德
I like your style, Scofield.
可乐先生  还需要点别的吗
You need anything else, Mr. Cole?
不用了  小姐  谢谢
I'm all right, little lady.
惠斯勒先生  你以前到底有什么计划
What was your plan, Mr. Whistler?
到底是什么计划
What was your plan?
单星...
Shan Xing...
科尔・普发没有参加我们的会面
Cole Pfeiffer did not arrive for our meeting.
这么说你没有拿到锡拉了?
So you don't have Scylla?
单星  下次吧...
Next time, Shan Xing.
如果有谁找我的话  我在洛杉矶
I'll be in Los Angeles if anyone needs me.
第二张卡下载好了  继续第三张
Number two down, on to number three.
我们设法窃取了丽莎的电话
We manage to get anything off Lisa Tabak's phone?
我不知道
I don't know.
除了卡  我什么都没拿
I didn't pick up anything but the card.
对于你在那做的那些事
I want to thank you
我表示感谢
for what you did back there.
我要你帮我做些事
I need you to do something for me.
好啊  不是每个人都行哦
Yeah, doesn't everybody.
我在找那个杀了我儿子的人
I'm looking for the man who killed my son.
你要什么
What do you need?
这里是警方的报告
Here's the police report.
我要你进入...
I need you to get
FBI的数据库...
into the FBI database
找到一份资料
and find a profile.
这个人是职业杀手
This man is a professional assassin.
黑白混血  六英尺高
He's African-American, six foot, four.
大约重220磅
About 220 pounds.
这只给你一个人看
That's for your eyes only.
你好
Hi.
你没事吧
Hey, are you all right?
没事
Yeah.
我想没事
Yeah, I think so.
我很担心你  你去哪了
Well, I was worried. Where are you?
我来接你吧
Let me come get you.
不用了  我快到家了
No, it's okay. I'm almost home.
听着...
Um, listen...
你  是唯一让我还活着的理由
You're what's keeping me going right now.
你也是我唯一拥有的了  而这也正是让我害怕的
And you're all I have left, and that scares me.
我只是想和你在一起
I just want to be together.
我知道这坏境和理想的还不能比
I know the circumstances are a little less than ideal,
但至少我们在一起
but we are together.
你在这里  我在这里
You're here, I'm here.
不用再等"总有一天"  而是...
It's not "one day" anymore, it's, um...
而是现在拥有
it's today.
你为什么不回来...
Well, why don't you come back
咱们一起吃吃饭...
and, uh, we'll make some dinner
聊聊天  共享二人世界...
and maybe find a little time for ourselves.
好的  我马上就来
Okay, I'll be right there.